(upbeat music)
So at this point of the course,
you're already pretty good at working with the DOM.
But there are still a ton of things to learn.
So to do that,
in this section,
we will build a beautiful website project
with a lot of different components
and visual effects that require
some pretty advanced DOM manipulation techniques.
So after this section,
you will have all the tools that you need
in order to implement any visual component or effect
that you can imagine.
Now, many of the things that I'm gonna show you here
could actually also be added to a webpage
simply by using a third party library.
But you want to master JavaScript and the DOM, right?
And so therefore,
you need to know how to do things yourself.
And so let's go learn advanced DOM manipulation now.
(upbeat music)